漫威《神盾局特工》前情回顧
Previously on "Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
梅  你的腿
May. Your leg.
你還沒完全恢復
You're still not 100%.
我無法知道
There's no way
你是不是說了實話
I can tell for certain if you're being honest.
但他可以
But he can.
只有我和西蒙斯
It's just me and Simmons.
她們說的是實話  她們兩個都是
They're telling the truth. Both of them.
我替你掩蓋了
I covered for you.
-你也可以讓別人讀到你的想法  -對
- You can let other people read your mind, too. - Yeah.
這是個低溫冷凍艙
It's a Cryo-Freeze Chamber.
我要走遠路過去
I'm taking the long way there.
你沉睡期間
While you were asleep,
我得以展開了一項計劃
I had time to put a plan in motion.
等我拿到賣了你的錢
With the price I'll fetch for you,
我就終于可以
I'll finally have the means
永遠離開這個可怕的地方了
to leave this horrendous place once and for all.
她是世界毀滅者
She's the Destroyer of Worlds.
直接讓她決戰生死吧
She should fight to the death.
漫威出品
只能湊合下了
Gonna have to do...
格蕾琴
Gretch.
這是給你的盒子
Got your tin right here.
我出一個代幣
I'll give you a token.
就一個
A token?
我以為至少能換三個
I was hoping for at least three.
我就能出這么多了
Token's all I can spare.
誰讓你是我最喜歡的客戶呢
Only for my favorite customer.
賽徹斯  我今天還不夠
Citrus, look, ‭I don't have enough today,
但也許明天就能
but maybe tomorrow, you can...
對不起  孩子
Sorry, junior.
今天沒有贈品
No gimmes today.
我不需要你的施舍
Look, I don't need charity, all right?
只要你最好的報價
Only your best offer.
我們一直在找你
We've been looking for you.
卡塞亞斯在繁育異人拿來賣錢
Kasius is breeding Inhumans to sell.
他有自己的恐怖科學部什么的
Guy's got his own cronenberg science division and everything.
所以才會來了這么多飛船
This would explain all the ships arriving.
你覺得他們是為了黛西而來嗎
You think they're here for Daisy?
估計是
Afraid so.
還是沒有梅的消息嗎
And still no sign of May?
通常來說  她對付得了克里人
Normally, she could hold her own against the Kree.
但她的腿狀態不好
But her leg -- it's in bad shape.
你們在這里啊
There you are.
泰絲  怎么了
Tess, what is it?
藍臉人
It's the Blues.
他們來收孩子了
They've come to harvest the children.
神盾局特工
第五季 第六集
那是卡拉巴夫人
That is Lady Karaba.
她是個瘋狂的野蠻人
She is a demented brute.
她對人的喜愛猶如詛咒
Her affection a cursed to anyone who receives it.
這是參議員蓋烏斯·普納瑞
And there is Senator Gaius Ponarian.
我看到他  就覺得反胃
I am... repulsed by the sight.
就連他最親近的朋友
Even the man's closest friends
也覺得他的脾氣就像一個有病的小野獸
find his temperament to be that of a diseased child monster.
看來卡塞亞斯真是聚集了最壞的人渣
Seems Kasius has assembled the worst of the worst.
別害怕
Do not fear.
你比這間屋子里的
You are far more reprehensible
任何人都更名聲狼藉
than any other creature in this room.
多謝你了  伊諾克
Thanks for that, Enoch.
別客氣
You're quite welcome.
構建你的假身份
It was a rather fun pursuit,
還挺有趣的
constructing your alias.
你不再是利奧波德·菲茲
No longer are you Leopold Fitz,
而是  波什托克
but instead, Boshtok,
一位擁有無盡財富的卑鄙太空掠奪者
a vile space Marauder of unlimited wealth.
這個胸牌真有必要嗎
Was the brooch really necessary?
有必要
Indeed.
胸牌代表了
That medal signifies
你取過的敵人性命數目
the number of enemy lives you've taken.
只是  感覺有點怪
Just... seems a little odd
戴著塊鑲了小水鉆的胸牌
wearing a medal ‭with little rhinestones on it.
你真逗
That is quite amusing.
你肯定知道那是蓋格酷幼蟲
You no doubt realize those are Geg-ku larvae.
好了  這樣吧
Okay, you know what?
我們放下偽裝  找到其他人
Let's drop the charade, find the others,
然后殺出一條血路
and we'll shoot our way out.
每個人存活的幾率
The chances of survival would be less than 2%
將不到2%
for each individual.
那是珍瑪·西蒙斯
That is Jemma Simmons.
需要我安排介紹一下嗎
Would you like me to broker an introduction?
我為什么需要你把我介紹給珍瑪·西蒙斯
Why would I need you to introduce me to Jemma Simmons?
這是掠奪者規矩
It's Marauder protocol.
看看這群貪婪鬼
Look at the sniveling horde.
這些忘恩負義的家伙多年來一直嘲笑我
These same ingrates mocked me all these years,
現在卻聚在這里
yet now they hover about,
吵著要我青睞
clamoring for my favor.
我對這位掠奪者也不熟
I, too, am unfamiliar with the Marauder,
但聽說他非常富有
though his fortune is rumored to be vast.
你要我多留意他
You want me to keep an eye on him.
普納瑞  再次見到你真好  親愛的朋友
Ponarian, how great to see you again, dear friend.
卡塞亞斯
Kasius.
來這里總是很榮幸
It's a pleasure to be here as always.
感謝你的招待  卡塞亞斯
Thanks for your hospitality, Kasius.
珍瑪  是我  別轉身
Jemma, it's me. Don't turn around.
淡定
Just play it cool.
我好想你
I've missed you so much.
我在一個秘密軍事監獄里
You know, I spent six months locked up
被關了六個月
in an ‭off-the-books military prison --
更不用說在太空里冷凍了80年
not to mention 80 years frozen in space --
只希望能夠找到你
all just hoping to find you...
終于見到你了
and here you are.
我想通了一件事
You know, I realized something.
宇宙無法阻止我們
The universe can't stop us.
因為我們跨越了星系  穿越了時間
'Cause we've crossed galaxies. We've traveled through time.
我們在大西洋海底也活了下來
We've survived ‭the bottom of the Atlantic
只為了能在一起
just so we could be together.
這樣的愛
Now, a love like that --
比任何詛咒都強大
that's stronger than any curse.
而你和我  我們合力就不可阻擋
And you and I -- we are unstoppable together.
我
I...
我再也不想和你分開
I don't want to live another day without you.
珍瑪·西蒙斯  你愿意嫁給我嗎
So, Jemma Simmons, will you marry me?
我知道我說了要淡定
I know -- I mean, ‭I know I said, "Play it cool,"
但不是這么淡定
but I didn't mean play it this cool.
珍瑪
Jemma.
有什么問題嗎
Is there a problem?
我問了你仆人一個問題
I asked your servant a question,
但她沒理我
which she ignored.
抱歉
My apologies.
我的仆人只能聽見主人的聲音
My servitors are only allowed to hear the voice of their master.
是嗎
Are they?
那你跟我說說
Well, why don't you tell me
你的奴隸聽不見客人說什么
how your guests' needs are met
要怎么滿足他們的需求呢
when your slaves can't hear them?
好了
There.
謝謝
Thank you.
她堪稱楷模
This one is quite exemplary.
其實  她是和世界毀滅者
In fact, ‭she also traveled through time
一起穿越時間過來的
with the ‭Destroyer of Worlds.
可能也是她膚色如此無暇的原因
Which probably explains her flawless complexion.
她賣嗎
Is she for sale?
不單獨出售
Not independently.
她是捆綁項目
She comes as a companion,
因為她很擅長激勵毀滅者
for she is quite adept at motivating the Destroyer.
我發現  人們需要的
Well, I find the only motivation
唯一激勵就是痛苦
people ever really need is pain.
以及對痛苦的正確利用
And its proper application.
真有見地
A wonderful sentiment.
戴著這么引人矚目的胸牌
I should have expected no less from a man
理當有如此見識
with such an impressive brooch.
你去看看
I need you to go see
今天的收成都有什么
what has been reaped from today's harvest.
是什么  地球的食物嗎
What? Terran food awaits?
有很多  但收成指的是別的東西
A bounty, though the harvest is something else.
今天早些時候  我的手下
Earlier today, my men were carrying out
主持了泰瑞根變異
the process of Terrigenesis,
希望能為客人造出新的異人
hoping to produce new Inhumans for my guests.
如果客人有意的話
If any were so inclined.
那得看買下毀滅者之后
Depends on how many units I have left
我還剩多少錢
after I purchase the Destroyer.
據說  你的品味很昂貴
It is said you are a man of expensive tastes.
我們馬上就能知道你有沒有足夠的資本
We shall soon see if you have the resources
滿足這種欲望了
to support such desires.
每年
Every year,
卡塞亞斯都讓所有滿18歲的穿過泰瑞根迷霧
Kasius puts all the 18-year-olds through Terrigenesis.
是今天嗎
And that day's today?
不  是幾個月之前
No, that was months ago.
這些孩子還只是青少年
Most of these kids are barely teenagers.
他是負責人
That's the one in charge.
從低層一點點往上抓人來著
Been working his way up from the lower floors.
我猜這跟卡塞亞斯的盛大派對有關
I'm guessing this has something to do with Kasius' big party.
產品多  利潤就多
More products, more profit.
他是弗林特
That's Flint.
沒有人跟他說話安慰他嗎
He doesn't have anyone talking him through this?
他父母在一次更新時被殺了
His parents were killed in a Renewal.
維吉爾很喜歡這孩子
Virgil had a soft spot for the kid,
甚至教他如何飛行
was even teaching him to fly.
時不時給他點錢  幫他渡日
Gave him odds and ends to help him get by.
你應該去跟他說句話
You should go say something.
泰絲  這怎么回事
Tess, this is crazy.
我應該再有兩年才要穿過迷霧的
I wasn't supposed to get misted for another two years.
這樣你不用再等了
Just means you don't have to wait.
這會毀了我嗎
Is this gonna mess me up?
一切都會沒事的
Look, everything is gonna be fine.
穿越迷霧  沒什么大不了的
Going through the mist -- it's no big deal.
即使沒有一群土狼盯著
Terrigenesis is scary enough
泰瑞根變異也夠嚇人的了
without a bunch of hyenas watching.
也不是他們的錯
It's not their fault.
這些人全都被灌輸了同樣的謊言
These people have all been fed the same lie.
人們相信自己想要相信的事
People believe ‭what they want to believe.
顯然他們是要被送去屠宰的羔羊
It's obvious they're lambs being led to the slaughter.
但愿這些孩子都不會結殼吧
Let's just hope ‭none of these kids crust over.
如果我真轉變了
If I do turn,
至少我不會再來向你要殘羹剩菜了
least you won't have me coming around, begging for scraps.
我喜歡你來
I like having you come around.
孩子們  到時間了
Children, it is time.
沒事的
It's all right.
我們尋求恩賜
We seek a great bounty.
希望今天聚集在此的年輕人中
Hoping that one of the young gathered here today
有人能自我升華
ascends to something greater.
準備接受卡塞亞斯賜予你們的禮物
Prepare to receive your gift from Kasius.
我看不下去了
弗林特
Flint!
怎么回事
What happened?
-你呢  -沒
- Do you? - No.
我賣給你的那窩維羅尼辛怎么樣了
So, how are you faring with that Vrellnexian litter I sold you?
是挺難對付
It has been trying.
這些野獸真是很難控制
The savage beasts have proven quite difficult to wrangle.
他們可不是生來讓人抱的
Well, they're certainly not bred to cuddle.
他們是戰爭猛獸
They're creatures of war,
不是人類毛茸茸的小狗
the not the shaggy dog of men.
但我本希望
But I had hoped
維羅尼辛會給你帶來小小的勝利
that the Vrells would provide you a small triumph.
上次我們聊的時候  被流放的重擔似乎
Last time we spoke, the strain of your exile seemed to...
讓你的靈魂不堪重負
wear heavy on your soul.
我可沒被流放
I was never exiled.
我父親只是希望我親自監督他的地球計劃
My father simply wanted me to oversee his Earth project personally.
而你哥哥則在監督家族帝國
While your brother oversees the family empire.
卡塞亞斯從未讓我做過戰士  直到今天
Kasius never offered me as a fighter till today.
看來這是我救你一命的下場
Guess that's what I get for saving your life.
我沒叫你救我
I didn't ask you to help me.
你希望我救你
You were hoping for it.
你腦子里是這么想的
In your brain.
對讀心人來說沒什么差別
Which is basically the same thing for a mind-reader.
情況開始有利于我們了
Things are starting to turn in our favor,
所以相信我  行嗎
so just trust me on this, okay?
我真的很慶幸我的抑制器現在開著
I'm really glad ‭my Inhibitor's on right now
就聽不到你腦子里的蠢主意了
so I can't hear whatever dumb idea's in your head.
我們需要合作
We just need to work together.
別再以為你有什么選擇了
Stop thinking that you have a choice.
我們是奴隸
We're slaves.
我很抱歉將你卷了進來
I am sorry for getting you mixed up in all this.
希望我們不需要互相殘殺吧
Let's just hope one of us doesn't have to kill the other.
親愛的朋友們  卡塞亞斯
Dear friends, in honor of Kasius
為大家獻上了世界毀滅者
presenting the Destroyer of Worlds,
我也為大家準備了
I, too, have brought a rare delicacy
一道珍貴的佳肴
for everyone's enjoyment...
新鮮的山達爾蝸牛
fresh Xandarian snail!
你太慷慨了  普納瑞
You are far too generous, Ponarian.
等開始競價的時候  務必記住這一點
Please keep that in mind when the bidding begins.
你是怎么將這里的人口
How do you keep your human population
控制得這么好的
so well under heel?
他讓他們自相殘殺
He has them kill each other.
換我也會這么做
Well, that's what I would do.
人類顯然占大多數
Humans clearly have the numbers,
所以必須讓他們恐懼
so fear is essential.
而最難辦的是
And getting them to do it --
讓他們來動手
that is the trick.
儀式化很有用
Ritualization helps.
將一切粉飾成一場游戲
Making it sort of a game.
真的非常有效
It's all very efficient, really...
至少就我的經驗而言
...at least in my experience.
看來我們所見略同
Seems we have similar minds.
這是非常有效地
It has done wonders
壓制了人類反叛的沖動
tamping down the humans' more rebellious impulses.
希望大家都享受這頓宴席
Well, I hope everyone's meal has been to their liking.
接下來即將進行的生死決戰
As for your more primal appetites,
則能滿足你們最原始的欲望
a fight to the death is moments away.
最后看一眼他們
So, take a final look.
其中一位異人
One of these Inhumans
很快就要從市場上撤下來了
will soon be withdrawn from the marketplace.
掠奪者
Marauder...
你還沒嘗你的蝸牛呢
you have yet to taste your snail.
也許低俗的人
Perhaps unrefined men
無法領略此等珍饈的美味
don't have the stomach for such indulgences.
我覺得
I find...
潮濕的生物
moist creatures...
很惡心
...distasteful...
就像將它們吞咽下去的肥嘴
...much like the fat mouths slurping them down.
跟這位波什托克一起用餐真有意思
This Boshtok makes for a lively dinner companion.
我們先將這些蝸牛放在一邊吧
Let us leave these snails to shrivel, huh?
還有更精彩的表演等著我們呢
Much greater pursuits await our attention.
也許那孩子的能力是消失
Maybe the boy's ability is to disappear.
不  這里面有鬼
No, this is something else.
他死了嗎
Is he dead?
怎么可能有人就這樣消失了
How does someone just disappear like that?
我也不確定...
I'm really not sure...
但我有個猜測
though I may have a theory.
-我們得回大集市  -那不安全
- We got to get back to The Exchange. - It's not safe for you.
-但那些守衛會找我的  -是為了賣了你
- But the Guards will be looking for me. - Only to sell you.
但我能過得更好
But I get a better life
同層的人也能受益
and the rest of the level profits.
你不會過得更好
You get no better life.
買下其他人的人都不是好人
People who buy other people are not good people.
他們只會傷害你
They'll only hurt you.
你又不知道
You don't know that.
你怎么做到的
How did you do that?
-泰絲  -你沒事吧
- ‭Tess. - Are you okay?
有事
No.
我剛被一個瘋女人綁架了
I was just kidnapped by a crazy woman.
這點孩子可沒說錯
Yeah, the kid ain't wrong about that.
別擔心  她和我是一起的
Don't worry. She's with me.
弗林特  這是悠悠球  她也是異人
Flint, this is Yo-Yo. She's Inhuman, too.
我差不多猜到了
Yeah, I kind of figured that already.
你們不是住在克里人層嗎
Why aren't you living down on the Kree levels?
我不是這里的人
I'm not really from here.
我們都不是
None of us are.
她不是唯一和我們一起的異人
And she's not the only Inhuman with us.
你是說他也是嗎
You mean this guy?
不  他就這么氣派
No, he's just cool.
我們不能永遠躲在這里
Look, we can't hide in here forever.
這會兒卡塞亞斯的人肯定在到處找弗林特
Kasius' men will be looking for Flint even as we speak.
吉爾去找站長匯報了
And Grill's reporting to his station boss.
晚上他就會回來
He'll be back end of day.
我們得在那之前趕緊消失
We need to disappear long before that.
我可以申請拖曳船作業
Look, I could put in for a Trawler run.
我們把弗林特藏在禁閉室里然后離開這里
We hide Flint in the brig and head out.
能給我們爭取個幾天
Could buy us a couple days.
但是沒有梅  我們沒有人能駕駛
Yeah, but without May, we don't have a pilot.
這是小事
Least of our worries.
要幫手嗎
Want any help?
人越多  越容易招疑
More people, more questions.
我最好一個人去
Best I go on my own.
待在這里
Stay right here.
我馬上回來
Be back in a few.
有你這樣的人加入我們真令人耳目一新
It is refreshing ‭to have a man of your caliber join our ranks.
愿意和我一起觀看展示嗎
Would you care to join me for the upcoming display?
等不及見識你要給我們看的每個人了
I'm eager to see everyone you have to offer.
那我可得盡我所能不讓你失望了
Then I shall make every effort not to disappoint.
第一位選手擁有無與倫比的能力
Our first contestant possesses extraordinary skill --
心靈感應  他能感知對手的戰略
a telepath, able to read his opponent's plan of attack
哪怕對方尚未執行
before it is carried out.
通常我會讓本和其他異人對打
Normally, I'd pit Ben against another Inhuman.
但為了今天的貴客
Yet, for this select crowd,
我決定挑選一位特別的對手
I've decided for a more unique opponent.
這一位來自別的時空
One not of this time.
訓練這位致命殺手的
This deadly assassin was trained
是銀河系最臭名昭著的組織
by one of the galaxy's most despised organizations.
但最有趣的是
But most intriguing,
她也是世界毀滅者的朋友
she is also a friend to the Destroyer of Worlds.
各位貴賓
Dear guests...
請允許我向你們介紹
may I present to you...
神盾局特工  梅琳達·梅
...Melinda May, Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
你這是作弊
You're cheating.
而你就要死了
And you're dying. ‭
有多少人和毀滅者一起穿越了時間
How many traveled in time with the Destroyer?
我只發現了
My servant and Melinda May
梅琳達·梅和我的仆人
are the only ones I've discovered,
但是錫納拉堅信還有更多人
though Sinara remains convinced there are more.
讀心者打斗很熟練
The mind reader's a skilled fighter.
看來訓練很刻苦
Speaks well of his training.
本在異人中算天賦頗高的
Ben is quite talented for an Inhuman.
但他在我父親的軍隊里一天都活不下去
But he wouldn't last a day in my father's army.
你對你父親的評價很高
You speak highly of your father.
他是我所知最偉大的戰士
He's the greatest warrior I know.
聽普納瑞的話  好像
Ponarian made it seem as if
你被從你的母星驅逐了
you'd been banished from your home world.
普納瑞是不知情
Ponarian knows not of what he speaks.
我父親就不看好我
My father was disapproving.
為了得到他的尊重  我做了不少事
The things I did to earn his respect...
留下了不少傷疤
...they left scars.
我的故事
My own situation --
則是誤解帶來的悲劇
it is ‭a tragic misunderstanding.
現在沒人能幫你了
No one can help you now.
就連卡塞亞斯的客人都不行
Not even a guest of Kasius.
你在懷疑自己
You're doubting yourself.
別刺探我的想法
Stay out of my head.
我猜你拍賣毀滅者
My guess is ‭you're selling the Destroyer
是為了改變他的看法
as a way to redeem yourself.
我相信大筆的財富
I believe a great fortune
能夠撫平一切罪過
can smooth over any transgression.
我愿意幫助你
I'm prepared to help you with that.
別覺得是我壞
Don't make me the bad guy.
卡塞亞斯把我扔進來
Kasius only tossed me in here
就是因為我幫了你的朋友
because I helped your friends.
好
Okay.
那我就不殺你了
Then I won't kill you.
多謝你無謂的承諾
Thanks for promising not to do something you can't --
沒有思考  直接動手了
Didn't think, just did.
我們必須合作
We have to work together.
你們怎么那么看重團隊合作
What is it with you guys and teamwork?!
這場打斗得馬上結束
This fight needs to end now,
不然他們會把我們兩個都送去地表喂蟑螂
or else they'll feed us both to the Roaches on the surface.
不行
No way.
卡塞亞斯現在不會改變規則的
Kasius isn't gonna change the rules now.
你只需要知道該問誰
You just have to know who to ask.
這場打斗讓我覺得無聊
This fight bores me.
我向你保證它會以令人興奮的方式結束
I assure you it will end in a most thrilling fashion.
錫納拉  讓守衛多扔些武器進來
Sinara, have the guards throw in more weapons.
問題不在缺少武器
Lack of weapons is not the problem.
我是來看毀滅者戰斗的
I came to see the Destroyer fight,
不是這種過氣的老古董
not some ancient has-been.
恐怕必須要失一命
I'm afraid a life is owed.
把那個神盾局特工送到地表去
Send the Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D. to the surface.
維羅尼辛會比看膩了的觀眾
The Vrellnexians ‭will have much more use for her
更想見到她
than your weary audience.
守衛
Guards!
送這個女人類去地表電梯
Escort the human woman to the surface lift.
謝謝
Thank you.
不幸的是  你的朋友只是拖延了必然之事
Unfortunately, your friend just delayed the inevitable.
沒人能逃過蟑螂之口
No one can escape the Roaches.
你見過那個男孩嗎
Have you seen the boy?
弗林特
Flint?
沒見過
Can't say I have.
他一直在這層混
He's a total floor rat.
可能去了任何地方
He could be anywhere.
或者...
Or...
是你把他藏起來了
...you could be hiding him.
我為什么要那樣做
Why would I do that?
我在儀式上看到你們在一起
I saw you together at the ceremony,
你跟他道別來著
offering the boy last words.
聽著  弗林特
Listen, Flint --
他能給我找到別人找不到的東西
he gets me things no one else can.
安慰那孩子
Giving the kid a pep talk?
只是想穩定我的商務關系
That was me just keeping my business relationship on the steady.
如果我發現你對我有所隱瞞
If I find ‭you're keeping things from me...
后果會很嚴重
there will be consequences.
明白
Understood.
說完了嗎
We done here?
為什么我還沒有擁有超能力
Well, how come I don't have my powers yet?
你已經擁有了
You have your power.
只是還沒有顯現
It just hasn't revealed itself.
你的能力用了多久才出現
How long did yours take?
那簡直是場災難
Oh, it was a total disaster.
我三周前因為吃魚湯
I crusted over three weeks earlier,
和墨西哥卷餅而結了殼
after eating fish soup and tacos.
墨西哥卷餅是什么
What are tacos?
這是什么鬼未來
What the hell kind of future is this?
墨西哥卷餅是種食物
Tacos are a food.
總之  我跟自己說  我是在做夢呢
Anyways, I had told myself this was just a dream.
然后我堂弟弗朗西斯科來了電話
And then ‭my cousin Francisco calls
說他媽媽出了事
with bad news about his mom.
我很難過  就去拿瓶啤酒  然后一下
I was upset, so I went to get a beer, and -- whoosh!
我又回到了沙發上  啤酒已經在手里了
I'm back on my couch, beer in one hand.
我意識到  我需要個瓶起子
I realize I need a bottle opener,
然后又一下  我又回到沙發上了
and whoosh again -- I'm back on my couch,
瓶起子已經拿在另一只手里了
bottle opener in the other hand.
你以為是怎么回事
What did you think was happening?
我的心跳得好快
My heart was beating so fast,
我以為是有人在我酒里放了可卡因
I thought someone ‭had put cocaine in my beer.
別說那個啊  大毒梟
Dial it back, Escobar.
我好擔心  就叫堂弟弗朗西斯科過來
I got so worried, I told my cousin Francisco to come over.
他花了好幾小時勸我別去接受驅魔
He spent countless hours talking me out of an exorcism.
這故事很有趣
That is a great story.
卡塞亞斯肯定會想親耳聽到的
Pretty sure Kasius is gonna want to hear that for himself.
我為這讀心人出一萬
10,000 for the telepath!
卡塞亞斯不需要錢  他想要的是武器
Kasius doesn't need money -- he wants weapons.
五門科文里恩大炮
Five Culverian Blasters.
這是拍賣  卡拉巴夫人  不是跳蚤市場
This is an auction, Lady Karaba, not a flea market.
拿著你沒用的玩具回你來的那個泥坑去吧
Take your useless toys back to the mudpits you crawled out of.
抱歉了二位
My apologies to you both,
但我不能賣掉這名異人
but I cannot in good faith sell this Inhuman.
你想什么呢  卡塞亞斯
What dense thought rattles in your brain, Kasius?
如果我想憑白被人撩撥
If I wanted a tease,
就去基特森的妓院了
I would have visited the brothels of Kitson.
你壓抑的欲望與我無關
Your pent-up desires do not concern me.
至于我的理由
As to my reasoning...
或許你愿自己跟客人們說
Perhaps you would care to illuminate our guests.
不  求你
No. Please.
不會有下次了
It won't happen again.
我錯了  求你
I was wrong. Please!
我之前問毀滅者是否有其他人跟她
You see, Ben was present when I asked the Destroyer
一同穿越時間時  本也在場
if others had traveled through time with her.
她堅稱我的仆人是唯一一個
She insisted that my servant was the only one,
但這并非實話
which turned out to be untrue.
卡塞亞斯  不怪他  卡塞亞斯
Kasius, th-- ‭it's not his fault. Kasius!
他撒謊了
He lied.
一般來說  這不會影響他的出售
Normally, that would not preclude him from being sold.
但這次  他是對我撒謊了
Only in this instance, that lie was told to me.
真有必要嗎
Is this really necessary?
讓哪個買家管教他好了
Make one of the buyers discipline him.
你應該是最能理解的
You of all people must understand.
有榮譽感的人  怎能容忍他的奴隸
No man of honor can allow the tongues of his slaves
如此公然撒謊
to lie so boldly.
是我  這要怪我
I'm the one -- I am the one to blame!
-不是本  -或許吧
- Not Ben! - ‭Perhaps.
但他沒那么有價值
But he's far less valuable.
別怪自己
Don't blame yourself.
不
No!
本
Ben!
不
No!
希望  這個展示更合你的胃口
Hopefully, you found this display more to your liking.
你回來早了
You're home early.
我以為又是叫我來做報告呢
Thought I was getting called up for another damn report.
結果  我的經理是想告訴我
But turns out, my manager just wanted to let me know
有個拖曳船的飛行員在角斗場里戰斗
that a Trawler pilot was fighting in The Crater.
-梅  -她沒事吧
- May. - ‭Is she all right?
我可不會用"沒事"來形容一個被丟去
"All right's" not a word I would use for someone
喂蟑螂的人
who was chucked out as Roach food.
或許該說  "一小口"
"Morsel," maybe.
現在  你該告訴我
Now it's time you tell me why
你們三個為什么會沒有生物表
the three of you didn't have any Metrics.
我們是從過去穿越來拯救世界的
We came from the past to save the world.
你是指...
Are you -- you speaking of...
預言嗎
the Prophecy?
我雖然是個土包子
Hey, look, I may be a rube,
但只有蠢貨才會相信那套預言的蠢話
but only dumb rubes believe in that prophecy nonsense.
但等我把你們四個
Though I will be a rich rube
交給了卡塞亞斯  我就會有錢了
once I turn you four in to Kasius.
你把我們交出去  我們就死定了
You turn us in, we're all dead.
聽著
Listen.
只要那死變態給我錢
Once that creepy son of a bitch pays me off,
我才不管他拿你們怎么辦
he can do whatever he wants.
死
Now, being dead...
可能還是你們最好的選擇
...might be your best option.
我很遺憾
I'm so sorry.
本救了我
Ben saved my life --
他救了我們
he saved both of our lives --
卡塞亞斯卻
and Kasius just...
就那么殺了他  而我只能看著
murdered him while I stood there.
你也做不了什么的
There was nothing you could do.
我要殺了他
I'm gonna kill him.
那你得排隊了
Well, you'll have to get in line.
你現在能聽到了
So you can hear now?
菲茲騙卡塞亞斯開啟了我的聽力
Fitz tricked Kasius into turning my hearing back on.
-菲茲怎么會在這兒  -我不知道
- How is Fitz even here? - ‭I don't know.
他突然就冒了出來  還有自己的飛船
He just showed up out of nowhere with his own spaceship.
挺厲害的
It's a baller move.
還有他那副賞金獵人的樣子
Not to mention the whole bounty-hunter look he's rocking.
我還是更喜歡他穿羊毛衫的樣子
I still prefer him in cardigans.
你知道他在計劃什么嗎
Do you have any idea what he's planning?
我不確定
‭Yeah, I'm not sure, actually.
我們還沒撈著機會講話
We haven't had a moment to speak,
但他似乎是來買我們的
though it would seem he's here to purchase us.
要是沒成功呢
What if it doesn't work?
我有把刀
I have a knife.
不至于吧
We can do better.
我沒多少刀具可選
Well, there was limited cutlery to choose from.
不  我是說我們的計劃  我們得想辦法合作
No, with our plan. We have to figure out a way to work together.
卡塞亞斯必須在打斗開始后關閉抑制器
Kasius has to turn my Inhibitor off before the fight starts.
我們到時再行動
We can make our move then.
你要打誰
Who are you facing?
可犧牲的人
Someone disposable.
菲茲肯定會準備好的
I'm sure Fitz will be ready.
又是這樣了
Here we are again.
我們對抗世界
Us against the world.
快來  有情況
You must hurry. There's a situation.
我們有麻煩了
We have a problem.
又怎么了
What is it now?
又有人來向卡塞亞斯
Someone new has arrived to acquire
購買世界毀滅者了
the Destroyer of Worlds from Kasius.
比我還有錢嗎
Someone more wealthy than me?
也更可怕
And more feared.
他哥哥
His brother.
為什么卡塞亞斯讓人在樓下打斗  吉爾
Why does Kasius have people fighting downstairs, Grill?
找樂子的游戲
All part of the fun and games.
希望他不會選你
Let's just hope he doesn't choose you.
他還是個孩子
He's just a kid!
我開始覺得  澤夫并不該死的
I'm starting to think that Zev didn't deserve to die.
或許是你女朋友陷害了他
That maybe your girlfriend set him up.
我可不非得把你們完好無損地交上去
Nothing says that I gotta turn you in cherry.
或許  我該繼續電電你們
So, you know, maybe I will just watch you sizzle.
停下  小子
Hey, knock it off, junior.
-我不知道怎么控制  -那就想辦法
- I don't know how. - ‭Well, you figure it out!
弗林特  看著我
Flint, look at me.
這是你的天賦
This is your gift.
你可以控制它的
You can control it.
住手  否則我就開槍了
You stop it, or I will stop you.
卡塞亞斯
Kasius.
我怎么聽說你哥哥來買毀滅者了
What is this about your brother coming for the Destroyer?
失陪一下
If you'd excuse me...
多棒啊
Isn't it wonderful?
從我母星過來路程遙遠
The journey from my home world is significant,
父親一定是非常看重
so Father must be quite serious
才會派福奈克親自來
if he sent Faulnak in person.
我也不是鬧著玩的  我向你保證
I'm also serious, and I guarantee you
我來這兒的路程要更遙遠
I have traveled a much longer journey.
能請到你  我非常榮幸
And it has been a privilege having you.
不
No.
我必須得到毀滅者
Not if I don't get the Destroyer.
你保證過我會有機會競價
You promised me a chance to make an offer.
我樂意提供這個機會
Which I look forward to entertaining...
但我還是建議你
though I would encourage you
考慮我其他的異人
to consider one of my other Inhumans.
看來并不順利
That did not appear to go well.
希望其他的事不會再出錯
Let's hope the rest does.
那好
Okay, then.
我還有件事需要你去做
There's one last thing I need you to do.
我們的命運近在眼前  錫納拉
Our fate is soon at hand, Sinara.
很榮幸你能到場  哥哥
It is an honor to have you join us, brother.
這人類糞坑有什么榮幸可言
There is no honor to be found in this human cesspool.
可你還是來了
Yet here you stand.
肯定有什么東西
There must be something of worth
值得你如此遠道而來
for you to travel such a great distance.
我來僅僅是因為父親有命
I'm only here ‭because of Father's orders.
很高興父親派了你來
It pleases to hear Father sent you,
他最信任的信使
his most trusted messenger.
這個毀滅者最好如你所言
This Destroyer had better be what you say,
否則我會很樂意提醒你我發火時的各種樣子
or I'll gladly remind you of the many shapes my anger takes.
是啊
Yes.
你一向急于展示
You were always quick to offer a demonstration.
或許現在  我也可以展示一番了
Perhaps now I can present one of my own.
毀滅者將要跟我最
The Destroyer is set to battle
厲害的一名異人對決
one of my most prized Inhumans --
我才不想
I have no desire
看你的本土試驗品打斗
to see one of your ‭homegrown experiments fight.
毀滅者必須面對一名克里戰士
The Destroyer must face a Kree warrior.
你的跟班就行
Your stray shall suffice.
但錫納拉并沒做好戰斗準備
But Sinara is not prepared for battle.
她不是你最厲害的戰士嗎
Is she not your greatest warrior?
看你躲在她身后的樣子  讓人這么覺得
You cower behind her as though she is.
或許我錯了
Perhaps I have misjudged
你不再想獲得父親的認可了
and you no longer seek Father's approval.
沒問題
Of course.
錫納拉會樂意出戰的
Sinara would be honored to fight.
好吧
Well...
我知道這很突然
...I understand this is sudden,
但也是極佳的機會
but it presents a tremendous opportunity.
我所努力爭取的一切
Everything I have been striving for
都看這一場打斗了
is but one fight away.
決一死戰
To the death.
是的
Yes.
就是要這樣
That is what has been promised.
我完全相信
I have every confidence
你會讓我們看到精彩的場面
that you will provide us all a great spectacle.
我待不下去了
I can't be here anymore.
等等  外面太危險了
Hold on. It's too dangerous out there.
那也比就盯著我剛殺的人好
It's better than staring at the guy I just killed!
我認識他
I knew him!
他是我最好的客人之一
He was one of my best customers.
有時還多給我一兩個代幣
Even gave me spare tokens from time to time.
吉爾的事不能怪你
What happened to Grill is not your fault.
你別無選擇
You had no choice.
他當時要殺我們
He was gonna kill us.
邁克和我  我們去找泰絲
Now, Mack and I -- we're gonna go find Tess,
然后帶你上一架拖曳船  好嗎
and we're gonna get you on a Trawler, okay?
去吧
Go.
這孩子該在打球
Kid should be playing ball
或競選學生會
or running for student council.
或是生活委員
Or class treasurer.
-這么明確  -我做了三屆呢
- That's pretty specific. - ‭Ah, served three terms.
我是個很對金錢負責的人
I'm a pretty ‭financially responsible dude.
把異人交出來
泰絲
Tess.
她不肯交出弗林特他們就殺了她
They killed her because she wouldn't give up Flint.
她已經死了
She's already dead.
我們現在只能
The only thing we can do now
讓弗林特不會落得同樣的下場
is try to keep Flint from meeting that same end.
走吧
Come on.
現在  壓軸戲開始
Now, our main event.
銀河系最致命的力量之一
One of the galaxy's deadliest forces.
但今晚  她將為取悅你們而戰
Yet tonight, she fights for your enjoyment.
親愛的朋友們  我向你們獻上
Dear friends, may I present to you...
震波女  世界毀滅者
...Quake, the Destroyer of Worlds?
這個小丫頭就是你的毀滅者
This puny girl is your Destroyer?
你太急著下判斷了
Your rush to judgment
這一向是你的短處  哥哥
has always been a shortcoming, brother.
我先關閉毀滅者的抑制器
Allow me to switch off the Destroyer's Inhibitor.
你就能看到她的真本事了
Then you shall see her true nature.
當然了  在那之前
Of course, before I unleash her,
我們得采取防護措施
we must take precaution.
要做一番開幕講話嗎
Would you care to give the opening commencement?
看來你的跟班不想再接受命令了
Seems your stray is done taking orders.
好啊  你個藍妖婊
All right, you freaky blue bitch.
我們開始吧
Let's do this.
這是為了本
This is for Ben.
守衛
Guards!
守衛  攔下他們
Guards, stop them!
我再不會離開你了
I'm never leaving you again.
那就娶我吧  菲茲
Then marry me, Fitz.
當然
Absolutely.
好了  來吧  我扶你
Okay, come on. I got you.
另外  我想說  我之前求婚了
Also, um, just to say, I did propose earlier...
但卡塞亞斯關閉了你的聽力
...when Kasius ‭had your hearing turned off.
當然了
Oh, of course you did.
不是  是真的
No, I -- Seriously, I did.
你好  朋友
Hello, friend.
你是誰
Who are you?
我是一個克里人
I am a Kree.
我一直都是  兄弟
As I have always been, brother.
你知道你在往哪去嗎
Do you know where you're going?
去那兒的人回不來的
People don't come back from there --
我不是個人
I am not a person.